#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/josephonischuk-ba8a60132 (LinkedIn)

# Joseph Onischuk

Senior Banker - Managing Director at BNP Paribas Greater New York City Area

#### Summary

Managing Director with proven domestic and international experience in developing business strategies and enhancing client relationships. Significant knowledge of the energy and commodities industry with a focus on the midstream and downstream oil & gas sector. A successful track record of developing new business, complemented by strong deal structuring, and motivating teams to deliver superior results.

## Experience

BNP Paribas 19 years

New York

Senior Banker - Managing Director 2011 - Present (9 years)

Responsible for leading the relationships and business development of a portfolio of publicly-traded midstream (MLPs) and refining companies. Focused on advising executive managements of strategic opportunities in Capital Markets (bonds, derivatives, and bank debt) and Corporate Finance.

Registered FINRA Series 79, 63

Head of Asia-Pacific Energy & Commodities Franchise Management 2007 - 2011 (4 years)

Responsible for developing and implementing the business strategy for the regional energy franchise with the objective of enhancing the firm's market position and profitability.

Managing Director 2001 - 2007 (6 years)

Houston, Texas

Responsible for developing and managing relationships with midstream and refining companies.

Barclays Investment Bank Director 1990 - 2001 (11 years) New York

Developed relationships with energy companies involved in the upstream, midstream, and downstream sectors.

Originated, structured, negotiated, and executed bank financing transactions including project financing, reserve based structured financing, and corporate borrowing.

Advised clients on appropriate capitalization and debt financing strategies.

Chase Manhattan Bank Assistant Treasurer 1982 - 1990 (8 years) New York

Management Training Program, Retail Branch Management (1982-1987) Credit Training Program (1987-1988)

Middle Market relationship management, Textile & Apparel (1988-1990)

### Education

Montclair State University
Bachelor's Degree, Marketing / Management · (1982)